Man...
Over here!
Ow!
Can you girls stop moving around?
Taichi!
Inaba! Did you find him?
No sign of him anywhere.
Damn, where'd he go?
Where'd he go?!
Go!
It was a bad idea to go to a
place with a lot of people.
We promised to visit the shrine
together as a club on New Year's.
As a club!
Club!
Pipe down, kids!
Inaba-neechan!
I bought takoyaki!
Ow!
Is that all you have to say for
yourself after making us worry?
Okay, that should be enough.
Taichi...
Here, open wide.
Huh?
You can't use your hands, right?
Uh, I can just ask them to let go.
Oh, sorry.
Fancy meeting you here,
Inaba-san, Yaegashi-kun.
Happy New Year.
Fujishima...
Why are the two of you
here together on this day?
Who are those kids?
Th-They're relatives!
And, uh...
StuCS was planning
on coming together,
but then we got stuck with these kids.
Yeah, yeah! What she said.
Oh...
Anyway, this girl looks
just like Nagase-san.
It's almost like Nagase-san
reverted back to childhood.
Oh, sorry!
We need to get going!
Huh?
Er, wait...
Where are we going?
Just hurry!
Ooh! I want this!
I'll buy something later!
How did we end up in this situation?
After we stopped having to
deal with unleashed desires,
we enjoyed a brief period
of peace and quiet.
The issue with Inaba and Nagase
was still up in the air,
but for the time being, nothing
had really changed between us.
But on the last day
of the second term...
What's this?
It was on the board when we got here.
But nobody remembers writing that.
It's almost 12:00...
What's wrong, Nagase?
I-It feels like my body's on fire.
Huh? Same here.
What's going on?
My clothes are too big!
Ooh, snacks.
Can I have some?
Huh? S-Sure...
Yay!
Let's share!
Uh-huh!
What's going on here?
What is this about?
Is something wrong with my eyes?
Something wrong with my eyes...
Yes, that must be it!
Okay, I'll close my eyes!
When I open them, everything
will be back to normal!
One, two, three, go!
This is so good.
Nothing changed!
What the hell?!
Okay, let's try this again.
Tell us your name and age.
Okay!
Kiriyama Yui! Eleven years old!
Nagase Iori. Six years old.
Next question.
Who is this lanky guy
with the dirty mind?
Aoki-san!
Aoki-oniichan!
You could have left off the last part!
What about the guy over
here who's pretty handsome.
Huh?
Taichi-san!
Taichi-oniichan!
Y-You're actually going to
compliment me, Inaba-san?
Okay, do you know why you're here?
No...
There you have it.
What do we have here?!
This makes no sense!
So basically, Nagase and Kiriyama
had their youth restored?
Yes. They're little kids again.
They don't understand
their current situation,
Here you go.
but they've adapted
to the circumstances,
so they don't question why they're here.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
It makes no sense at all,
but that's where we stand.
So is this Heartseed?
It has to be.
Maybe...
Wait...
Oh! They turned back!
Huh? What?
My underwear's all messed up!
Iori-chan...
We're in the room.
Then avert your eyes!
It looks like he's
reversing time this time.
Do you remember anything that happened
while you were a kid?
I don't think so.
But I kept remembering stuff
that happened when I was that age.
Like when I played with friends
and stuff from school.
And what was happening at home.
I was also remembering stuff
from when I was in fifth grade.
It was almost blindingly clear...
So clear, it's a little uncomfortable.
Wait, winter vacation starts tomorrow.
What if one of us turns into
a kid in front of our family?
It said 12 PM to
5 PM on the board.
If this phenomenon only
occurs during that time,
we can find a place to
hide out until it's over.
For now, the board is
all we have to go by.
There's a building near my house
that's about to be torn down.
We can go there tomorrow.
I'm home...
You're late, big brother!
Sorry, I had stuff to take care of.
More important than your
adorable little sister?
Well, it's Christmas, and
you have a girlfriend,
so you're probably busy.
I don't have a girlfriend.
Well, I was getting close,
but something else has come up now.
Like, you didn't get her a present?
There are bigger issues to worry about.
Ah! Wait, big brother!
Heartseed?
Yes, I am Heartseed.
But I'm not.
Yes, you can call me Number Two.
Wh-What do you mean?
You're not Heartseed?
I am Heartseed.
But I am not the Heartseed you know.
So I'm Number Two.
You're just like Heartseed.
But you're a different person?
I need you to become a knight.
Knight?
It would be difficult if
everyone became children.
That would be unsustainable.
It's your job to make
sure that doesn't happen.
I will be watching.
This won't last long.
However, you must not tell
anyone else about me.
If you do,
the 12 PM to 5 PM phenomenon
will never end.
What are you talking about?!
What's your relationship
with Heartseed?!
What was I doing?
Did I really turn into a kid?
Yeah, I think so.
Oh...
Will Taichi not like me anymore
after seeing the past me?
He's not that kind of person, I guess.
T-True, I guess.
What kind of girl talk is this, anyway?
It's laughable that you and I are
even talking about this stuff.
But when you consider that we're
in love with the same guy,
it becomes pure comedy.
No kidding.
I never thought that you and
I would get to talk like this.
Mom's home.
Sorry, Inaban. See you tomorrow.
Yeah, see you to—
No way! Why did you quit?
A lot happened...
Then what about your promise?
Promise?
Yes, your promise! You promised me!
Oh, Taichi.
H-Hey. Is this a friend of yours?
Y-Yeah...
Mihashi Chinatsu-san.
A friend from when I practiced karate.
Oh, this is Yaegashi Taichi-kun.
What? Is he your boyfriend?
No, we're on our way
to a friend's house.
He's not my boyfriend.
Nope, absolutely not.
He's definitely not my boyfriend.
How many times do you need to say that?
Sorry, we need to run.
Ah, Kiriyama!
I won't accept it, Kiriyama!
Mihashi-san and I faced each
other in tournaments a lot.
She was more a rival than a friend.
A rival...
That's amazing.
I never knew you lived
in that sort of world.
I used to.
But I haven't seen Mihashi-san
since she moved.
And I quit karate.
She mentioned something about a promise?
Uh-huh, but I can't
remember what that was.
I'm fine. What about you?
Okay, I'll get home as early as I can.
Nagase...
Whoa!
Taichi! Yui! Hello!
Why are you together?
D-Don't tell me that
after landing Inaban,
you're targeting Yui?
Huh? What was that about Inaban?
I-It's nothing, Kiriyama!
Ooh, this place is pretty comfy.
Is someone going to shrink today?
I'm still having a hard time
believing that it happened.
I'm burning up!
No way!
What's going on?!
So cute!
Oh, she's adorable!
You can find traces of the
cool beauty she'll become
in the lovable nature
only a child can have!
It's even better when you
realize that this is Inaban!
Uh, this is no time to be celebrating.
Girls are crazy.
Ah, that was bliss.
That was enough cute to get
me through a long time.
You girls need to control yourselves.
She's scared now.
I feel bad now.
Me too.
Sorry, Himeko-chan.
No! I just came close to sympathizing
with Nagase and Kiriyama!
Himeko-chan, what do you want to drink?
Orange juice.
Here you go.
Oh, wait.
Here.
Thank you.
I want Coke!
Here you go.
Yay!
Thanks, Nana's big sister.
Nana?
Aren't you Nana's sister?
No?
What's he talking about?
Yoshifumi-kun, do you know my full name?
Yaegashi Taichi-san.
What about her?
Nagase Iori-san.
And what about her?
Isn't she Nishino Nana's sister?
Um, I'm Kiriyama Yui...
Kiriyama Yui?
Oh, you sure look like her.
Oh, that's a good job.
You already know how to write your name.
Amazing.
We can already see signs
of Inaba's brilliant mind.
I win! I was faster!
Darn!
What were you doing?
Exploring the building.
And racing each other.
I won.
That's why you haven't
kissed anyone before!
What?! I-I already
told you that I have!
Wait! What are you talking about?!
Technically, I was Inaban,
but it was me on the inside,
so that counts as my first kiss!
I've made up my mind!
Na-Nagase... Don't say another word.
Was I supposed to hear that?
What's a kiss?
You don't need to know yet, Himeko-chan!
This is grown-up talk!
Will I become a grown-up
if I kiss someone?
That's not how it works.
You're supposed to wait until
you've grown up to kiss someone.
When will I kiss someone?
I'd say by the fall of your
first year of high school...
Wait, that doesn't matter right now!
Hey, what about their clothes?
Huh?
What happens to their clothes
when they turn back?
Their clothes won't change...
Crap! We need to change their clothes!
Get outta the way, Taichi! Quick!
G-Got it!
Come on, Himeko-chan.
What am I supposed to do?
Hurry up!
Turn around and close your eyes!
O-Okay!
Hey! You too, Yoshifumi-kun!
No, it's too late!
That hurts!
And my clothes are so tight!
Wait a second!
Why am I naked?!
Ah! Wait, Inaban!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
I was ten years old?
It's so creepy to not remember
anything that happened for five hours.
So the words on the board
were meant as a hint.
I'm guessing it's significant
that only four names are on there.
Does that mean Taichi is the only one
who won't have his time reversed?
Heartseed will probably show up to
explain everything at some point.
He sure is taking his time.
Oh, whose is this? Can I have some?
I have a question for you.
Do you know who Nishino Nana is?
How do you know that name?
When you were ten, you thought
I was Nishino Nana's big sister.
You said that I looked just like her.
She was a girl my age
who lived nearby.
And...
I went out with her in my
first year of middle school.
Huh?
But she moved away at the
end of the school year.
After that, we exchanged New Year's
cards for a while, but that was all.
If she were a high school first-year,
would she look like me?
Possibly.
Doesn't that mean...
You weren't yourself back there.
Well, I would have expected
you to be like, "I love Yui!"
You wouldn't understand
since you haven't
had your time reversed.
After you turn back, the
memories from that time
are still fresh in your mind,
so I got confused.
Confused?
I remembered how much I loved Nana,
and I couldn't deny that.
I do love Yui.
But I used to love Nana.
So when did I forget that I loved Nana?
Are my feelings gone?
Or do they still exist?
Tell me, Taichi...
What does it mean to love someone?
Sis...
Wh-What?
What's going on?
I thought you never wanted to
look at those things again
after you quit karate.
Oh, I happened to remember
a few things from the past.
Right, I ran into Mihashi-san today.
That's this person.
I used to talk to her a lot.
And she's visiting relatives
in this city right now.
She'll only be here for
winter break though.
Oh...
Why did you quit karate, Sis?
I loved to watch you doing karate.
Sis? What's wrong?
Did I say something wrong, Sis?
I'm sorry. Stop crying, Sis.
Nagase...
Taichi!
What a coincidence!
Uh, we're headed to the same place,
so it's not that odd.
Taichi, can I ask you for a favor?
What?
Can you watch me closely when
I'm a kid, just for a bit?
To see what I was like.
Is that because
you want to know what
the real you is like?
No, that's not it.
At first I figured I wouldn't
think about it too much,
but given the circumstances,
that's impossible.
If you were given the
chance to redo your life,
would you take it?
Well, there are a lot of instances where
I wish I did something different.
I...
Huh?
I would want to redo my life.
And I would want to do
a better job this time.
Aoki Yoshifumi! Eleven years old!
Nagase Iori! Fourteen years old.
It's so cold outside!
I can give you my gloves, Iori-chan.
Oh. It's okay, Taichi-san.
No need to be shy.
Here.
Thank you very much.
They're so warm.
That look of satisfaction on his face...
Then to show my appreciation...
I love you, big brother!
B-Big brother?!
I had a feeling that you
liked being called that.
I do, but how did you know?!
Women's intuition?
Scary...
This is what Nagase was
capable of when she
switched personas to
match the situation?
Stop smirking like a fool, big brother.
Wow, the two of you are so in sync.
Like a real couple!
Huh?
T-Taichi and I look like a real couple?
Yes!
R-Really? You're such
a good girl, Iori-chan!
Okay, I'll buy you something nice!
Thank you very much!
Say nothing of it!
What should I choose?
She even won Inaba over.
The sky's the limit!
Fourteen-year-old Nagase
Iori is a monster.
So this is what Nagase meant
when she said she used to
switch between personas?
So, what was I like as a kid?
Was I kind of shy?
Well...
You were scared of Nagase and Kiriyama,
but that was their fault.
Yeah, I was always scared.
I still am.
Everyone has things they
don't want people to know.
There are things you're
better off not knowing.
And there are things you don't want to
remember about yourself.
But this phenomenon is bringing our
past selves into the present.
As this goes on,
it could lead to disaster.
But we've managed to make it
through everything together.
So we should be okay.
I'm worried, Taichi.
I'm worried.
I already said that I don't
remember making any promise!
Stop cowering like a wimp.
Has your mom said anything?
You don't like Yui anymore, Aoki?
I forgot to live carefree.